BLAIR WARNER

blairthedesigner.com blairthedesigner@gmail.com 425.524.7910

I am a User Experience Designer who puts people first. With a background in graphic design and years of teaching experience, I am no stranger to problem solving. I love to make meaningful experiences and hopefully can make the world a better and happier place. I also enjoy drawing, practicing Japanese, and I have an unhealthy addiction to denim.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

OrbSense, Technologies LLC - Seattle. WA 8.2016 - 9.2016 Worked with stakeholders on a three week sprint for the development of a mobile application. Conducted research and interviewed potential users. Worked with a design team to create two iterations of the prototype app and conducted usability testing on each version.

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGN IMMERSIVE

General Assembly - Seattle. WA 6.2016 - 6.2016 Worked 70+ hours/week in six design sprints in an Agile development environment. Interacted closely with web developers, and clients

ENGLISH TEACHER

Ibaraki, Saitama and Tokyo, Japan 4.2006 - 3.2008 / 4.2011 - 3.2016 Worked in a total of 22 different elementary and junior high schools in the Greater Tokyo area. Collaborated with teachers to make lessons and activities tailored to different grade and skill levels. Acted as a cultural ambassador for my students. Participated in school functions and after school activities.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / LETTERPRESS PRINTER

Bell'Invito Letterpress Studio - Dallas, TX 2.2009 - 8.2009 Worked with clients, marketers, designers and printers to develop custom, couture letterpress stationery. Was also responsible for the creation of web graphics for the company website, and file preparation for die creation. Operaton of 19th-century letterpresses for printing and die-cutting, as well as assembly of stationery.

ASSISTANT GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Standard Deluxe, Inc. - Waverly, AL 5.2005 - 2.2006
Worked with clients, designers and printers to create designs for silkscreen printing. Worked with web developers to created web graphics and inputted data for the company website and web store.

EDUCATION

UX Design Immersive

General Assembly - Seattle, Washington 2016

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design

Auburn University - Auburn, Alabama 2000 - 2005

SKILLS

Affinity Diagram Comparative Analysis Competitive Analysis Concept Map Heuristic Evaluation Navigation Personas Prototype Site Map Sketch Storyboard Task Analysis User Flow User lourney User Scenario User Stories Wire frame

TOOLS

Axure
Balsalmiq
Illustrator
InDesign
Invision
Office
Omnigraffle
Photoshop
Sketch
POP